gettemplate.com 2002-12-11

# gettemplate.com - get your new site layout in one click

The GetTemplate.com Privacy Policy

GetTemplate.com is extremely concerned about protecting the privacy and confidentiality of our clients and customers and any information they submit to us.

No information that would identify individual users is sold or otherwise transacted by GetTemplate for profit. GetTemplate will use the information for its internal business purposes by its employees and authorized third party representatives, subject to confidentiality restrictions at all times. GetTemplate may use information to make other marketing offers to you only if you specifically authorize GetTemplate, to do so.

GetTemplate does not knowingly collect personal information from minors, i.e., persons under 18 years of age. If GetTemplate determines that information received is from a child, the information will be deleted. GetTemplate.com cannot confirm that a user is a minor, but requires a representation about each person’s status as competent to use the website and transact business. 

Aggregate reports are generated for GetTemplate’s statistical and tracking purposes. These reports do not contain any personally identifiable information and are not released unless required by governmental or judicial request, requirement or order.

When visiting any Internet site your unique address called an "IP address" is recorded. GetTemplate does not release any information about the collection of this address to any third party except pursuant to its internal business purposes, government or judicial request, requirement or order. GetTemplate archives the log files in order to create aggregate statistical reports, escrow tracking, detect errors at the web site, and for security reasons. The log files may eventually be deleted. 

GetTemplate employees are subject to confidentiality restrictions when accessing any such personal information and such access is limited to only those employees who have a need to know the information. 

No images, files, or cookies are downloaded from third party servers. GetTemplate generates cookies only for purposes of providing personalized services to users while they use the GetTemplate site. Users who do not wish to have cookies stored on their machines can disable them through browser options without losing core exchange functionality of the GetTemplate site.

For more information contact [privacy@GetTemplate.com](mailto:privacy@GetTemplate.com) GetTemplate customers also may verify their personal information that is on record at GetTemplate. To verify information or to have personal information removed from the GetTemplate database contact this e-mail address:[support@GetTemplate.com](mailto:support@GetTemplate.com)
